<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Angelo&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://antjowie.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Angelo&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 22:25:43 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://antjowie.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Introduction</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 15:20:18 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/introduction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The reason why I am writing this page is that during development I decided to switch to a whole other way to update my progression on this project. This page will discuss the progress up until now and what is left to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Foundation</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 14:59:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/foundation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This originally was the layout of the project, but during the development of this project, I noticed that it is better to document my progress on this project in a linear path instead of updating this list every time. Many ideas changed shaped during development. Not only because of oversights, but also because of new books I have read, new things I have learned. This page will not be updated anymore, but when the project is nearing a solid state will I start documenting the classes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The framework serves a role in the following subjects. The subjects are their responsibilities. Marked subjects are being worked on. Unmarked subjects aren&amp;rsquo;t. &lt;code&gt;(you can click the bold title to see the progress)&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Object Manager</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/object-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 14:36:52 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/object-manager/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A &lt;code&gt;Scene&lt;/code&gt; is a level or a section. A certain moment in the program where a certain group of objects are loaded. The main menu is a scene. The level is a scene. &lt;code&gt;Scenes&lt;/code&gt; are managers of objects.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utilities</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/utilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 19:57:14 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/utilities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some things just have to be saved. In our case configurations. To make life easier for both of us (computers and humans), data is saved in a special format. There are many formats that we can choose from. But because of my recent studying of Python and Web Development. My preference for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.w3.org/XML/&#34;&gt;XML&lt;/a&gt; (which I only used because of Tiled) shifted to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.json.org/&#34;&gt;JSON&lt;/a&gt;, a much more easier format, IMHO.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Manager</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/data-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 18:20:16 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/data-manager/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;Data Manager&lt;/code&gt; is responsible for the data. This is not to be confused with the &lt;code&gt;Assets Manager&lt;/code&gt; which is responsible for all the assets. The data are all the configurations. Keybindings, resolution, everything that has a string or integer attached to it. At a low level view the data manager is just a glorified map.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Input Handler</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/input-handler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 18:17:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/input-handler/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;Input handler&lt;/code&gt; listens to all events. It is the layer between everything the user uses to interact with the computer. It monitors the state of every key the user can press (or is supported).
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axios Framework Instance</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/game-instance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 21:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/axios-framework/game-instance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Instance&lt;/code&gt; is the main class of the framework, you could call it an instance of the framework, but it really is an instance of a game. &lt;code&gt;Instance&lt;/code&gt; is responsible for the timeline in the game. It is the main loop of the game.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axios Framework</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/projects/axios-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 13:53:09 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/projects/axios-framework/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Axios Framework makes use of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sfml-dev.org/&#34;&gt;SFML&lt;/a&gt;. The Axios Framework is a 2D game framework that runs on files made by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mapeditor.org/&#34;&gt;Tiled&lt;/a&gt;. The programmer only writes the objects. The objects are exported to a file that can be loaded in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mapeditor.org/&#34;&gt;Tiled&lt;/a&gt;, a 2D tilemap editor. At first, I wanted to make a game engine, but I have no experience making any kind of GUI yet. I believe that you should not do two major new subjects at the same time, so a framework it is. Hopefully, this project can one day evolve into a game engine.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Switch to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/post/the-switch-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 21:12:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/post/the-switch-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I used to have another portfolio site I made in preparation to enter the course &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nhtv.nl/bachelors/creative-media-and-game-technologies/introduction.html&#34;&gt;Creative Media and Game Technologies&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nhtv.nl/&#34;&gt;NHTV&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;https://antjowie.github.io/post/my-journey-towards-nhtv/&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;(I actually got a place in the course, read more about it here)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. By doing so I hoped to increase my chances during the conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NHTV will be renamed to Breda University of Applied Sciences as of September 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Problem is, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any prior knowledge of web development. So I started doing research. I always wondered how the web worked.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Journey Towards NHTV</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/post/my-journey-towards-nhtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 22:45:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/post/my-journey-towards-nhtv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve met many people who don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do with their lives. It is a hard question at such a young age: What do you want to become when you get older? You&amp;rsquo;re just starting to get more independent and you already have to make a decision that will shape your future.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building the gameloop</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/ray-shaper/building-the-gameloop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 20:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/ray-shaper/building-the-gameloop/</guid>
      <description>A bit of reflection This is one of the things that keep impressing me about programming. Every time when I make a solution it feels like the best solution I ever came up with. But I am programming I notice that it almost never is true. That also is the case this time.
One of the main issues that I had during the development of Runaway was my implementation of the parent class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a foundation</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/ray-shaper/building-a-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 17:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/ray-shaper/building-a-foundation/</guid>
      <description>After having brainstormed for a while, I decided to make a puzzle game based on the reflection of lasers. It is not the most creative game but I am interested in programming it. I will call the game Ray Shaper because you shape the ray using objects and your own glass shield. The objective is to get the ray to the door. Sounds pretty easy, right?
After having made my first game, there are many things I have learned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning is key</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/ray-shaper/planning-is-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 15:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/ray-shaper/planning-is-key/</guid>
      <description>Reflection is an interesting theme because I have never done anything with it. When I think about it, the first thing that comes to mind is light. Because ideas go away so fast I always write them down in a word web/mind map or some other kind of structure. This gives me an ordered overview of all my ideas and by doing that I can mix them together to make something interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ray Shaper</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/projects/ray-shaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 14:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/projects/ray-shaper/</guid>
      <description>When I was 13 I first heard about NHTV. I was in second grade and already started looking for a school to enter. Back then I was quite scared of the future. I realized the importance of the decisions we have to make right now and was afraid that I would choose something that wouldn&amp;#8217;t satisfy me. I don&amp;#8217;t feel that way anymore. I make sure that every decision that I make right now regarding my future will be the correct one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light part 1.1</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/light-part-1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 14:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/light-part-1-1/</guid>
      <description>Just a little note for you, this post is less about the project and more about me. You will notice that halfway through the text I&amp;#8217;m kinda changing the whole message of this post and it becomes less about the program and more about me. If you are not interested in that, you should stop after reading the following chapter.
 Back when I added gates to the program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light part 1</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/light-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 20:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/light-part-1/</guid>
      <description>This part will discuss the games light system. So let&amp;#8217;s start off with devising one. I&amp;#8217;ll first make a simple drawing so we&amp;#8217;re on the same page.
Simple drawing showing my idea of the light Pretty simple right! I thought so, this is by no means a complex game. If you do not the objective of the game yet, allow me to explain. Else you can skip over the following paragraph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movement of player part 3</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/movement-of-player-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 10:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/movement-of-player-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to one of my favorite things about programming, making up some kind of formula for your game.
While I was quite satisfied with my previous implementation of the movement system (it is my first time implementing collision), I still found it to be quite sloppy. It&amp;#8217;s probably a programmer&amp;#8217;s nature to think badly of their code like an artist thinks lowly of their drawings. I&amp;#8217;m both of these. So I decided to try and neaten some things up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animation and sprite sheet part 2.2</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/animation-and-sprite-sheet-part-2-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 12:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/animation-and-sprite-sheet-part-2-2/</guid>
      <description>Another day in the life of a programmer == another day for bugs. For those with a keen eye. You may have noticed something strange in my videos, or rather, something different. Take a look at these two videos before and after the animation handler class.
Before   After   Have you noticed it? The player seems to spawn in a different location. But I haven&amp;#8217;t changed anything regarding the spawn location or movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animation and sprite sheet part 2.1</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/animation-and-sprite-sheet-part-2-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 12:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/animation-and-sprite-sheet-part-2-1/</guid>
      <description>Hello, today we will discuss the problem surrounding the not that groundbreaking (or should I say game-breaking?) glitch seen in this video.
  Absolutely horrible! How could this happen? We will discuss that right here. This was the implementation.
// Brace for some ugly vector checkingif (newPos.x &amp;gt; 0 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; newPos.y == 0)m_animHandler.changeAnimation(playerDirection::Right);else if (newPos.x &amp;lt; 0 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; newPos.y == 0) m_animHandler.changeAnimation(playerDirection::Left); else if (newPos.x &amp;gt;= 0 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; newPos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movement of player part 2</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/movement-of-player-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 10:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/movement-of-player-part-2/</guid>
      <description>So to implement acceleration. The smartest thing to do would be to use real-life formulas. What can be more realistic or accurate than that? Oddly enough, I decided to use my own formula for it. I did it this way because I thought it would be more fitting for my game, while I&amp;#8217;m not so sure about the pros and cons, I decided to implement them both with different games. When I&amp;#8217;m going to make another game in the near future, I will use real life formulas for my game, Right now though, I&amp;#8217;m going to use my own implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movement of player part 1</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/movement-of-player-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 10:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/movement-of-player-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Implementing movement can be as simple as adding values to the players&amp;#8217; position to calculating their position with all kinds of forces integrated into a formula. Because Runaway will be a simple but quite challenging game, I will implement an acceleration based move set. This way, the player will need to think about how long he keeps buttons pressed, and I can add some interesting game mechanics to keep levels feel a bit different from each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animation and sprite sheet part 2</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/animation-and-sprite-sheet-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 20:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/animation-and-sprite-sheet-part-2/</guid>
      <description>To implement an animation handler you first have to know the order of the frames in the sprite sheet. Or perhaps the other way around. Or maybe you are way further ahead than me and have already made a class that can handle both situations. Either way, the implementation is the same, or should I say the meaning of it. Most sprite sheets work the same way as any sprite sheet you will see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animation and sprite sheet part 1</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/animation-and-sprite-sheet-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 15:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/animation-and-sprite-sheet-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Tools make us productive if you choose the right one for the job. When it comes to sprite sheets, there are a whole bunch of choices. I too have got my little bag of drawing tools which we will discuss below.
Because I&amp;#8217;m fairly new to game developing, I still program 2D games. Not that it is a bad thing, but I haven&amp;#8217;t even once touched 3D animations. This post is about Runaway so let us discuss the tools that I&amp;#8217;ve used to make this sprite sheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collision with static blocks part 2</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/collision-with-static-blocks-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 14:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/collision-with-static-blocks-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Finally! I have made the function work in all direction. It looks pretty nasty to the eye though and I&amp;#8217;m certain that there are way better implementations than mine, but just having it work makes me more than happy.
In the previous part which you can go to by clicking on this, I have implemented a function which calculates the distance between a block and the player. While this does work, it can get quite confusing when you continue to program since all the differences in length will be relative to the player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collision with static blocks part 1.1</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/collision-with-static-blocks-part-1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 16:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/collision-with-static-blocks-part-1-1/</guid>
      <description>In my previous part, my implementation for this function was very barebone. It really wasn&amp;#8217;t thought out well. So in this part, I will explain all my thoughts. So you can see how I calculated all of it.
I first made some basic sketches to see how the coordinates of the player and object relate to each other. You can see them here down below, although it really is unnecessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collision with static blocks part 1</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/collision-with-static-blocks-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 17:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/runaway/collision-with-static-blocks-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Normally part 1 starts at the planning phase, but I already started this projects before I made this site. With that out-of-the-way, let&amp;#8217;s discuss our problem.
With our basic move set done, we are ready to add collision. There are many ways to program collision. The way I&amp;#8217;ve chosen to do it is by calculating the vertical distance from the player to his first solid lower block. This way, when the distance is negative, we can snap the player back into a correct distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Runaway</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/projects/runaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 17:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/projects/runaway/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;gallery caption-position-bottom caption-effect-fade hover-effect-zoom hover-transition&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageGallery&#34;&gt;
	  
  
&lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;https://antjowie.github.io/css/hugo-easy-gallery.css&#34; /&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34; &gt;
  &lt;figure  itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;/img/runaway/Light-test-1.png&#39;);&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://antjowie.github.io/img/runaway/Light-test-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Light is a very important aspect in this game&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Working with light&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://antjowie.github.io/img/runaway/Light-test-1.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
  

&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34; &gt;
  &lt;figure  itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;/img/runaway/Ligth-example.png&#39;);&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://antjowie.github.io/img/runaway/Ligth-example.png&#34; alt=&#34;You have to start somewhere&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;A broad idea&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://antjowie.github.io/img/runaway/Ligth-example.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
  

&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34; &gt;
  &lt;figure  itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;/img/runaway/playerSpritesheet.png&#39;);&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://antjowie.github.io/img/runaway/playerSpritesheet.png&#34; alt=&#34;How do we process this spritesheet?&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Make him move&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://antjowie.github.io/img/runaway/playerSpritesheet.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://antjowie.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>angelo05rettob@gmail.com (Angelo Anthony Rettob)</author>
      <guid>https://antjowie.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Glad to know that you are interested in me as a person! A little thing before you start reading though.
Down here is a short description of who I am and what I can do. Further down is a small story of how I became who I am at the moment of writing this. If you want to contact me, just send me a mail at angelo05rettob@gmail.com. If you want to tell me to make a form to send emails, feel free to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>